When he came back from his, when
Мы, когда он приехал со своего, когда
summer came, we went to Sochi, then to Moscow,
лето, мы поехали в Сочи, потом в Москву,
and then to the Tursk region, we went to Moscow
а потом в Турскую область в Москву мы
, and then we flew home again
поехали, а потом уже домой опять
.  Understood?  So it turns out that
прилетели. Понял? То есть получается,
your dad killed people in Ukraine, and for
твой папа убивал людей в Украине, и за
that money you went on a trip to Sochi, right?  Well
эти деньги вы покатались в Сочи, да? Ну
, like, yeah, we're not going to skate now.  And
типа, да, сейчас мы не будем кататься. А
what do you think, I know what's
как ты считаешь, там я знаю, что
going on there.  Do you think
происходит. Как ты считаешь, правильно
your dad did the right thing by killing people in
ли делал твой папа, что убивал людей в
Ukraine?
Украине?
Hello.  Let's have a normal conversation.
Привет. Давай нормально пообщаемся.
Hello.
Привет.
Listen, I have a godfather, Uncle Sasha, he
Слушай, у меня кум, дядя Саша, он
says that Russian children are all good
говорит, что российские дети все хорошие
and they don’t support the war.  This is true?
и они не поддерживают войну. Это правда?
You don't support
Ты не поддерживаешь
the war?  Whose do you think
войну? А как считаешь, чей
Crimea is?  Well, I kind of have...
Крым? Ну я как бы у
Well, how can I explain it?
меня Ну как объяснить?
Just tell the checkers: Russia or
Просто скажи чекерам: Россия или
Ukraine?
Украина?
Well, I'm not against anyone or anyone.  I
Ну я не против никого и никого. Я
understood correctly.  I don't mind either.  Is Crimea
правильно поня. Я тоже не против. А Крым
Russia or Ukraine?
- это Россия или Украина?
Well, how can I explain it to you?
Ну как вам объяснить?
Just tell me: Russia or Ukraine?  Just
Так и скажи: Россия или Украина? Просто
say one word: Russia or Ukraine.
скажи одно слово: Россия либо Украина.
We have two Crimeas.
У нас два есть Крыма.
Understood.  Do you have any relatives
Понял. У тебя кто-то из родственников
fighting?
воюет?
My dad fought in the war.  Well, I'm home
У меня папа воевал. Так-то сейчас дома
now.  At home he is wounded.
уже. Дома он раненый.
He arrived 2 years ago.
Он 2 года назад приехал.
And how did he arrive?  And why doesn't he
А как он приехал? И почему он сейчас не
go to war now?
идёт на войну?
I forbid him.
Я ему запрещаю.
Dad was wounded.
Папа был раненый.
Dad was wounded.  Dad, where is the wounded
Папа был раненный. Папа куда раненый
dad?
папа?
And I remember he told me a story.
А я помню, он мне рассказывал историю. У
He had a broken rib for O. And did they pay him
него было ребро сломанное для О. А ему
for the injury
деньги за ранение
?  He was supposed to be given 2 million. And
выплатили? Ему должны были дать 2 млн. А
for the injury they gave him another 1 million. That's how it is.  3
за ранение дали ещё 1 млн. Вот так. 3
million?  Yes, I know.  Where did you spend this money
млн? Да, я знаю. А куда эти деньги вы
?
дели?
And
А
we, well, we copy when he came from
мы, ну, мы копи мы когда он приехал со
his, when
своего, когда наступило
summer came, we went to Sochi, then to Moscow,
лето, мы поехали в Сочи, потом в Москву,
and then to the Tursk region.  We went to Moscow
а потом в Турскую область. В Москву мы
, and then flew home again
поехали, а потом уже домой опять
.  Understood.  So it turns out that
прилетели. Понял. То есть получается,
your dad killed people in Ukraine, and for
твой папа убивал людей в Украине, и за
that money you went on a trip to Sochi, right?  Well,
эти деньги вы покатались в Сочи, да? Ну,
like, yeah, we're not going to skate now.  And
типа, да, сейчас мы не будем кататься. А
what do you think, I know what's
как ты считаешь, там я знаю, что
going on there.  Do you think
происходит. Как ты считаешь, правильно
your dad did the right thing by killing people in
ли делал твой папа, что убивал людей в
Ukraine?
Украине?
Well, if it's war, then it's war.  You cannot become dumb.
Ну, если война, так война. Немешь стать.
What city is your dad from?
Он он твой папа из какого города?
We don't live in the city.  Well,
Мы с ним не в городе живём. Ну, область
what area, region.
какая, регион.
And I won't talk.
А я не буду говорить.
Well, yes, well, it turns out that your dad went to a
Ну да, ну получается, твой папа поехал в
foreign country to kill people, so that he could then use the
чужую страну убивать людей, чтобы потом
money to go to Sochi.
на эти деньги покататься в Сочи.
No, at first he just decided to go.
Нет, он сначала просто решился поехать.
Yes.  What does dad say?  How does he
Да. А что папа говорит? Как онто он
feel some kind of conscience that he
чувствует какую-то совесть, что он
killed people?
убивал людей?
I don't know.
Я не знаю.
And what does mom say?
А мама что говорит?
Mama Si is not alive.  What about me?
Мама си не живёт. Меня очем.
Well then stop.  You live with your mother,
Ну так стоп. Ты живёшь с мамой и с
stepfather
отчимом
and two sisters.  Yeah.  Does dad
и с двумя сестрами. Ага. А папа отдельно
live separately?
живёт?
Dad lives with grandma.  Yes.  But with
Папа живёт с бабушкой. Да. Но на деньги
dad's money we went to Sochi.
папы поездили в Сочи.
And did your mother and stepfather go to Sochi too, or what?
А в Сочи ехала мама отчим тоже или как?
Or we went without my stepfather, the
Или без отчима ехали
first time we went with my dad
сначала в первый раз мы поехали с папой
and I
и я
went, and when we saved up for the second
поехал, а когда мы накопили уже второй
time, my grandma and grandpa went with us
раз, с нами поехала бабушка и дедушка
.
мой.
Understood.  So it turns out that without money from the war it was
Понял. А получается, без денег от войны
impossible to travel to Sochi?
не получалось ездить в Сочи?
We could have
А мы и так могли
saved up anyway.  And he just decided to do it himself.  He
накопить. А он просто сам решился. Он
wanted it himself.
сам захотел.
What do you think, your dad?
Как считаешь, твой папа?
Well, how can I
Ну как
explain it?  Well, if it's war, then it's war.  I
объяснить? Ну если война, так война. Я
can't say anything about this.  Well, what
ничего не могу сказать на это. Ну а ес
if you grow up and are
если тебя вот ты вырастешь и тебя
taken to war, will you also be like me?
возьмут на войны, ну тоже будешь меня?
Well, they hardly take girls.  Well, if they
Ну, девушек почти не берут. Ну, вот если
decide there that, yes,
там постановят, что, да, нужно будет
girls will have to fight too, and they take you,
воевать и девушкам тоже, и возьмут,
give you a machine gun, and you’ll kill me.
дадут автомат, будешь убивать меня.
I don’t know, in short, war is like war, I won’t
Я не знаю, короче, война как война, я не
go here.  Well, what if they take me?
пойду сюда. Ну, а если если возьмут, у
I was so nervous when I found out
меня столько нерва было, когда я узнала,
that my father had left.
что отец уехал.
Yes, well, look, you grow up,
Да, ну вот смотри, вот ты вырастаешь,
yes, a law is passed that all girls
да, принимает закон, что все девчонки
also go to war, so they send
вот тоже идут на войну, так отправляют
you to Ukraine.  Are you going to kill me?
тебя в Украину. Ты будешь меня убивать?
Is it possible to refuse to go to war there?
А там можно сделать отказ на войну?
You don't have to go.  I know how it can be done.
Можно не поехать. Я знаю, как можно.
Well,
Ну,
well, there is war, there is war.  War is war.
ну война есть, война. Война есть война.
Well, I'll have to choose.  either refuse, or
Придётся ж выбирать. или отказ, или
go to defend the homeland in
всё-таки ехать защищать родину в
Ukraine.
Украину.
I immediately chose refusal.  Fine.  Do you
Я сразу отказ выбрал. Хорошо. Как ты
think those people who went to
считаешь, те люди, которые поехали
kill people in Ukraine are heroes?
убивать людей в Украину, они герои?
Well, how can I say, I support
Ну как сказать, я поддерживаю
the country, but at the same time I feel sorry for the people who are being
страну, но мне одновременно жалко людей,
killed.  So you
которых убивают. То есть ты
support Russia attacking
поддерживаешь то, что Россия напала на
Ukraine, but you feel sorry for the dead Ukrainians,
Украину, но тебе жалко убитых украинцев,
right?
да?
I support the country, I do not support
Я поддерживаю страну, не поддерживаю
murder.  And as you see, look, your
убийство. А как ты видишь, смотри, твоя
country, uh, introduced troops into Ukraine, started a
страна ээ ввела войска в Украину, начала
war.  War already implies that
войну. Война уже подразумевает, что
people will be killed.  Well, how can I answer?
людей. Ну как я могу ответить?
I actually have a second cousin and a
У меня вообще есть бабушка троюродная и
grandfather who now live in the Tula
дедушка, которая сейчас живут в Тульской
region, and they are actually Ukrainians.  And I don't give a
области, а они вообще украинцы. И мне по
damn what
барабану какие они по
nationality they are, it makes no difference to me.  I will love
нации, мне без разницы. Я буду любить
them as they are.  Fine.
такими, какими они есть. Хорошо. Вот
Look, a Russian missile recently
смотри, российская ракета недавно
flew into the city of Sumy, into a residential
прилетела в город Сумы на ээ в жилой
area, killing a lot of people,
квартал, убило очень много людей, в том
including children.  In Krivoy Rog,
числе детей. В Кривой Рог на детскую
many children died on a playground.
площадку очень много детей погибло.
A lot of people fly into Kharkov.  Do you
Харьков прилетает очень много. Как ты
think that the fact that Russia is
считаешь, ээ то, что Россия этой войной
killing Ukrainian children with this war is normal
убивает украинских детей, это нормально
or not?
или нет?
How can I
А как мне
explain it?  Damn, I'm panicking right now.
объяснить? Блин, я сейчас на панике. У
I just have a few tears
меня просто немного слёзы
coming to my eyes.  Well, how can I answer?
появляется. Ну как я могу ответить?
In short, I can't answer.  Well, what should I
Я не могу, короче, ответить. Ну что
answer?  Well, look, Russian missiles are
ответить? Ну смотри, российские ракеты
flying into Ukrainian cities and killing
прилетают в украинские города и убивают
Ukrainian children, girls just like
украинских детей, таких же девочек, как
you.  Is this normal or not?  Well, what's so difficult
ты. Это нормально или нет? Ну что сложно
to answer?
ответить?
Well, that's not normal.  Well, war is war.
Ну ненормально. Ну война как война. А
What's wrong with you or is war just like
что ты то ненормально или война как
war?
война?
Well, how can I answer?  I'm not
Ну как я могу ответить? Я же не
our president.  Well, what do you think, is
президент наш. Ну ты как считаешь,
Russia doing the right thing or the wrong thing by launching its missiles at Ukrainian
Россия, пуская свои ракеты по украинским
cities and killing Ukrainian children
городам, убивая украинских детей, делает
?
правильно или неправильно?
Well, how can I explain it to you?  Explain it that way.
Ну как вам объяснить? Так и объясни.
My uncle Sasha, my godfather Sasha Zorin,
У меня дядя Саша, мой кум Саша Зорин,
really asked me to ask Russian
очень просил вот поспрашивать российских
children what they think.
детей, как они думают.
Well, I don't know how to answer.  I don't know.
Ну я не знаю, как я ответить. Я не знаю.
Well, how a Russian rocket is launched from
Ну как российская ракета выпускается из
Russia and lands in Krivoy Rog on a
России, прилетает в Кривой Рог на
children's playground.
детскую площадку.
Yes.  Is it good or bad that Russia
Да. Это плохо или хорошо, что Россия так
does this?  Do you support or not
делает? Ты поддерживаешь или не
?
поддерживаешь?
I have, how can I explain it to you?  I
У меня есть, как вам объяснить? У меня
have an ordinary character.  I have
есть обычный характер. У меня есть
love.  For what?
любовь. К чему?
Well,
Ну,
there is a war.
есть к войне.
Okay, let's not complicate things again.  Just
Так, ещё раз не усложняем. Просто
watch.  Russia launches its missile from
смотри. Россия выпускает свою ракету из
Russia, it flies into Ukraine and
России, она пролетает в Украину и
kills Ukrainian children.  Is Russia doing it
убивает украинских детей. Россия делает
right or wrong?
правильно или неправильно?
Well, still no.
Ну, всё-таки нет.
Wrong.
Неправильно.
Yes.  So you think that Russia is
Да. То ты, значит, считаешь, что Россия
doing wrong by killing people in
неправильно делает, что убивает людей в
Ukraine,
Украине,
so you don’t support Russia in this?
то ты не поддерживаешь Россию в этом?
Well, I pretend to support it in front of
Ну я притворяюсь, что поддерживаю при
people.  Not really.
людях. Так-то нет.
No, well, just now you thought about it for a long time
Не, ну вот сейчас вот ты же долго
, right?  What do you think, if Russia
думала, да? Как ты считаешь, если Россия
is doing it wrong, why is it taking you so
делает это неправильно, почему ты так
long, why can’t you immediately
долго, почему ты не можешь сразу
say it’s wrong?
сказать, это неправильно?
Well, how can I explain it to you?  I am from Russia myself.
Ну как вам объяснить? Я сама из России.
I think
Я думаю,
who is to blame now Okay.  Who is to blame
кто виноват в сейчас Хорошо. Кто виноват
for Russia's war with Ukraine?
в том, что Россия воюет с Украиной?
Well, news helps.
Ну, новости в помощь.
I'm bad at watching the news.  I'm interested in
Я плохо смотрю новости. Мне интересно,
what you think.
как ты считаешь.
Did you know
А ты знал,
that Zelensky started it?
что Зеленский начал?
I heard something, but not exactly.  Can you
Слышал что-то, но не совсем. Можешь мне
tell me what exactly he started?
рассказать, что именно он начал?
Oh, wait, the dog is asking to come to me.  I'll
О, он подожди, ко мне собака просится. Я
let the dog in now.  Walk fast.
сейчас запущу собаку. Быстроходи.
[music]
[музыка]
Well,
Ну,
tell me how Zelensky, so, tell me
расскажи, как Зеленский, так, расскажи,
how Zelensky started the war.
как Зеленский начал войну.
Well, he called our
Ну, он позвонил нашим нашему
president and
президенту,
said, "Well, like the
сказал: "Ну, типа
usual hello."
обычно привет".
Well, how can I explain it to you in a
Ну, как вам объяснить в
nutshell?  I don't remember all this.  He sort of
сокращении? Я это всё не помню. Он типа
said hello and said that he had said a lot of things
поздоровался, сказал, что много чего он
about our country.  And in the end
говорил про нашу страну. И в итоге в
he said: “Let’s fight.”  Something like
конце сказал: "А давай воевать". Типа
this.  Ugh, you're not that.  And who
так. Фу, ну ты не это. А кто кто тебе
told you that Zelensky told
рассказал так, что Зеленский сказал
Putin: "Let's fight."  I'm in I'm
Путину: "Давай воевать". Я в Я в я
watching the news.
новости смотрю.
Understood.
Понял.
Damn,
Блин,
what do you
как ты
think, those people from Russia who are
считаешь, те люди из России, которых
sent to Ukraine and they kill
отправляют в Украину и они там убивают
Ukrainians there, are they heroes of Russia or are they
украинцев, они герои России или они
murderers?
убийцы?
Well, how can I
Ну как вам
explain it to you?  Half a hero is more of a
объяснить? Наполовину героя больше всего
killer.  Most of all a killer.  How is that
убийцы. Больше всего убийца. А как это
half a hero?  What is heroism?
наполовину героя? В чём героизм?
Why did they decide to go there?
А что они решились поехать туда?
Ah, and therefore nothing more.  Nothing
А, и поэтому больше ни в чём. Больше ни
else.
в чём.
Is your dad a hero or?
А твой папа герой или?
Well, if he is a father, I can say,
Ну, если он отец, я же скажу,
I can say that he is half a hero.
я могу сказать, что он герой наполовину.
What is your father's heroism?
А в чём героиз твоего отца?
I already answered that he decided to go there himself
Я уже отвечала, что он туда решился сам
.   Are
поехать.
you proud of yours?
Ты гордишься своим?
I'm only proud of the medals.  What
Горжусь только за медали. Какие
medals?  Ah, a medal for bravery, a medal from the
медали? А, медаль за отвагу, медаль от
president, a medal for the capture of Bakhmut,
президента, медаль за взятие Бахмута
and some other one and several more medals.
и ещё какая-то и ещё несколько медалей.
I don't remember.  Do you know what
Я не помню. А ты знаешь, что такое
Bakhmut is?
Бахмут?
Oh, [ __ ], I don't
Ай, блин, я не
remember.  It was a city with a population of
помню. Это был город, в котором жило
70,000 people.  Your dad and A is a
70.000 людей. Твой папа и А это
Ukrainian city, right?  Your dad and other
украинский город, да? Твой папа и другие
people completely destroyed this city.
люди уничтожили полностью этот город.
70,000 people were destroyed.  And for this
70.000 людей уничтожили. И за это твои
your dad was given a
твоему папе дали
medal.  Are you proud of this medal?
медаль. Ты гордишься этой медалью?
Your dad was in prison before the war.
Твой папа в тюрьме сидел до войны.
He was taken from prison to war.
Его же на войну с тюрьмы взяли. Да
No, he went himself, he filed it himself, he
нет, он сам поехал, он сам подал, он сам
filed the application himself from prison.
подал заявление из тюрьмы.
No.
Нет.
Okay, look.  Medal for the capture of Bakhmut.
Так, смотри. Медаль за взятие Бахмута.
This is because your dad and others like
Это за то, что твой папа и другие такие
your dad destroyed a city of
как твой папа уничтожили город, в
70,000 people.  70,000 people were
котором жило 70.000 людей. 70.000 людей
destroyed near
уничтожили под
Bakhmut, I watched it on the Internet.
но Бахмута смотрела в интернете.
Why did your dad get a medal for
За что твоему папе дали медаль за
Bakhmut?
Бахмут?
I don't know
Я не знаю,
what he's talking about,
что он засгу
you can.
что можешь.
I can now
Я могу сейчас
google what they can do.  Yes.  Maybe?
загуглить за что они могут. Да. Может А
Can you, can you call your dad?
ты можешь, а ты можешь папе позвонить? А
Or are you talking on the phone now?
или ты по телефону сейчас говоришь? Да
No, I'm on the computer.  It's night time for me now
нет, я по компьютеру. У меня сейчас
.  What?  Can you call your dad and
ночь. Что? А можешь папе позвонить,
ask him why he got the medal?
спросить, за что ему дали медаль?
Bakhmut is
Бахмута
not allowed now.  It's night for me.   It's
сейчас нельзя. У меня ночь.
3:00 am here,
У меня 3:00 ночи,
right?  And good.  So it turns out that you
да? И хорошо. А вот получается, ты
are proud of your dad’s medals?
гордишься этими медалями папы?
Well, how about it, 50/50?
Ну как, 50 на50?
What about 50?  What 50?  Tell.
А что 50? Что 50? Расскажи.
Well,
Ну
like half pears, half not.
типа наполовину груш, наполовину нет.
Why are you proud?
А почему гордишься?
Damn, I don’t remember what I said then,
Блин, я не помню, что я тогда говорила,
what I’m
за что я
proud of.  I said something to dad
горжусь. Я папе что-то
.  I don't really remember.  Do you understand
говорила. Так-то не помню. Ты понимаешь,
that the
что
father of
папа
some Ukrainian child is raising some
какого-то украинского ребёнка какую-то
little girl?
девочку маленькую?
Well, yes, I understand someone like
Ну да, я понимаю,
you, but in Ukraine he killed her, and they
такую как ты, но в Украине он её убил, и
gave him a medal for it, and you are 50/50
ему за это дали медаль, и ты 50 на50
proud of it.
этим гордишься.
I don't mind that he killed
Я не гружусь за то, что что он убивал
people.  I'm saddened that he sort of
людей. Я гружусь за то, что что он типа
got them.   What do you
их получил.
mean you received it?
В смысле получил?
Well, I'm not proud of what he
Ну я горжусь не за то, что что он
kills, but I'm proud of what he
убивает, а горжусь за то, что что он
gets.  And did he receive
получает. А что он получил
medals?  So he received medals for
медали? Так медали он получил за
killing Ukrainian people and Ukrainian
убийство украинских людей и украинских
children.
деток.
Well, what does this have to do with me?  War is war.
Ну а я тут же причём? Война это война.
That is, once again, you understand that
То есть ещё раз, ты понимаешь, что
your dad was given medals for
твоему папе дали медали за то, что он
killing people in Ukraine, including
убивал в Украине людей, в том числе и
children, and you are proud of it.
детей, и ты этим гордишься.
How to explain?
Как объяснить?
Wait, can I just talk?  Remember, you
Стой, можно я просто загу. Помнишь, ты
asked why he was given a medal for the
спрашивал, за что ему дали медаль за
capture of Bakhmut?  Yes.  Look,
взятие Бахмута? Да. Смотри, ты мне
just tell me differently.  Why did your
просто по-другому скажи. А зачем твой
dad take Bakhmut?
папа брал Бахмут?
His commander assigned it to him.
Его командир ему так назначил.
So, why did the commander order us to take
Так, а зачем командир назначил взять
Bakhmat?
Бахмат?
I don't know.
Я не знаю.
And you didn’t ask your dad why you
А ты не спросила у папы, а зачем вы
destroyed Bakhmut?
уничтожили Бахмут?
What do you think is needed to
Как ты считаешь, что нужно, чтобы
stop this war?
остановить эту войну?
I don't know.  Reconcile the presidents.
Я не знаю. Помирите президентов.
Well, your president doesn't want to
Ну так ваш президент не хочет
make peace.  He wants your dads to
мириться. Он хочет, чтобы твои папы и
continue conquering Bakhmut.
дальше Бахмуты завоёвывали.
At first, Zelensky didn’t want it when
Сначала Зеленский не хотел, когда
our Russians offered it.
русские наши предлагали.
What did your Russians offer?
Что ваши русские предлагали?
I remember the news said that our
Я помню в новостях говорили, что наши
Russians suggested that they make peace about a year ago
русские предлагали где-то год назад им
, and now Zelensky himself
помириться, а сейчас Зеленский сам
said that he wants to make peace.  Well, how should
говорил, что хочет помириться. Ну как
this be understood?  You have some kind of
это понимать? У вас делают какие-то
patriotism lessons, where they talk about the war
уроки патриотизма, там про войну
.
рассказывают.
How can I explain it to you?  We didn't have a
А как вам объяснить? У нас не было
lesson, but we were tested.
урока, но нас проверяли.
How did you check?
Как проверяли?
Well, like, when our village is
Ну, типа, когда на наш посёлок
attacked, we’re like, how should we
нападут, мы типа как мы должны
hide, how should we run out.  And this is
прятаться, как мы должны выбегать. А это
civil defense.  Understood.
оборона гражданская. Понял.
Yes.
Да.
Why do you go to chat roulette and
А зачем ты в чат рулетку выходишь и
choose Ukraine?
выбираешь Украину?
Quiet.  Mom came into the
Тихо. Мамка зашла в
room.  Everyone who was whining there wrote
комнату. Все, кто там ныли, писали
this, calm down.  It justifies and
цеж, успокойтесь. Это оправдывает и
glorifies the murder of your
глорификует убийство ваших
children.  This is just the video for my uncle Sasha's club
детей. Это как раз для моего клума дяди
.  You forget that these people go to
ролик. Вы забываете, что эти выходят в
chatroulette and choose Ukraine.  Yes, she is
чатрулетку, выбирают Украину. Да, она
proud of her
гордится
father's medals for Bakhmud.
медалями отца за Бахмуд.
She
Она
will grow up and weave nets.  She
вырастет, будет плести сетки. Она
will grow up and carry humanitarian aid.
вырастет, будет гуманитарочку возить.
She will grow up and assemble drones
Она вырастит, будет дрончики собирать
for
для
boys.
мальчиков.
You are the one who is worried about her.  Switch,
Это вы переживаете за неё. Переключи,
switch.  Skip, skip, skip, switch,
переключи. Скип, скип, скип, переключи,
switch.  And she doesn't care.
переключи. А ей плевать.
They ask that a Russian
спрашивают, что российская
missile flies into a Ukrainian city and
ракета прилетае по украинскому місту и
kills Ukrainian children.  What is good or what is
вбиваю украинских дітей. Це добре чи
bad?  And she
погано? И вона
thinks, she thinks for a long time,
думае, вона думае долго,
well, 50/50 and so
ну, 50 на50 и так
on.
далее.
Whoever is taking on the
Хто приймается за
Russian
российских
military killing of Ukrainian
ризных выт вбивство украинских
children now is leaving you, you must
детей зараз покидейна вы повинні
go for the Ukrainians and Ukrainian
перемась за украинців и украинских
children and not for
детей а не про
God, she knows what she knows, she knows everything
боже вона знае что ж вона знае всё во
perfectly well
прекрасно
.  They come out here with a clear
знаю. Воны выходят сюда с чтким
purpose, with medals from their father and son.  Over there the
намером, медальками папы з бахвата. Вона
homeland is already
родина вже
zipped.  Today she is honoring the medals of her
зипсована. Сегодня вона радие медалькам
father from Bakhmut, right?  And tomorrow the stinks will
папы из Бахмута, да? А завтра вони будут
hold a parade at the school.  And the day after tomorrow,
проводити парад в школе. А післязавтра
school graduates will sign a
ці выпускники школы підуть підписувати
contract and storm the
контракт и штурмувати
landing, and we’ll help and scream
посадку, а вона будем помагати и кричаг
you were 8 years old.
вы были 8 лет.
All.  You get the signs
Всё. Звидки у вас береться якась
because you feel so sorry for them, you
така жалість до них звідки у вас
get the signs because, let’s say, you feel so sorry for
збереться якась, скажем, бажання бути
people before them.
людяним до них.
FPV drones will then give the command and
FPV дроны таким потім дадуть команду и
run to kill you and that’s it.
вони побежуть вбивати вас и всё.
As long as you don’t start
Поки вы не почнете
to get involved
вноситись
with the philistines of Russia, there will be no sense in the axis of such
до мешканців России, як до ось такого
absolute
абсолютного
evil
зла толку не
.  The Axis will be victorious.  Otherwise, start
буде. Ось буде перемога. А то вже
wondering who is good with him,
шукайте, хто там з ним був хороший,
bad, poor thing, not poor thing.  And immediately, hi stinks,
нехороший бедняжечка, не бедняжечка. А
subscribe to my Telegram right now,
дуппишись на мій й Telegram прям зараз
axis vn and
ось вн а
popik, it is even more and more important YouTube is
попик це дуже и дуже важливо YouTube
banning us through Skargeor in the shadow ban
заганяе нас чере скаргеор в тіньовий бан
and the video is no longer shown to people,
и дуже багато відео не показуется людям
information about the stream is not shown at all times
вчасно не показуется інформація про
in order for us to be less operational
стрими для того щоб ми мали оперативний
Sign up to subscribe right away And the pop up
зв'язок підпишиться прямо зараз А попик
there in the telegram is also useful and
там в телеграмі окмде ще теж є цікава и
useful information and we ask you
корисна інформація и мы повин з вами
to make a permanent operational link
тримати постійний оперативный зв'язок
without showing you about it on
незалежно від того чи покаже вам про цей
YouTube.  Glory to Ukraine!  Subscribe!
YouTube. Слава Украине! Підпишись!